justhungry.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy | JustHungry

It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating JustHungry.com.

### Website Visitors

Like most websites, JustHungry.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. JustHungry.com's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how JustHungry.com's visitors use its website. From time to time, JustHungry.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

JustHungry.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments. JustHungry.com only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

JustHungry.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on JustHungry.com's behalf or to provide services available at JustHungry.com's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using JustHungry.com's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. **JustHungry.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone**. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, JustHungry.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when JustHungry.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of JustHungry.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an JustHungry.com website or have subscribed to receive updates from JustHungry.com and have supplied your email address, JustHungry.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with JustHungry.com and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. JustHungry.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. JustHungry.com uses cookies to help JustHungry.com identify and track visitors, their usage of JustHungry.com website, and their website access preferences. JustHungry.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using JustHungry.com's websites, with the drawback that certain features of JustHungry.com's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If JustHungry.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that JustHungry.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of JustHungry.com may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on JustHungry.com may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. For more information about this practice and to understand your opt-out choices, please click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. For information about Google Adsense, one of our advertising partners, please visit this page: [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by JustHungry.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, JustHungry.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Contact

If you have any questions or comments pertaining to the information presented on this page, please contact us. 

#### Footnotes

This Privacy Policy document is an adapation of the Privacy Policy on [Automattic.com](http://automattic.com/), available under a [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/) license.

_Last updated June 14, 2015_
